Sam Altman predicted AI would
create the first one person
billion dollar company. It just
happened and it's not what
you think. Matthew Gallagher built
a telehealth company called Medvi
from his living room in
LA. He sells GLP1 weight
loss drugs online. He outsources
the doctors, the prescriptions and
the shipping. His only full
time hire. His brother He
he spent $20,000 and two
months building the whole thing.
ChatGPT and Claude wrote his
code midjourney and Runway made
his ads. 11 labs and
custom AI agents handle customer
service. First year revenue $401
million. This year Medvai is
on pace for 1.8 billion.
No massive team, no venture
backed army of engineers. Just
one founder and AI doing
the work of hundreds. Altman
said this would have been
unimaginable without AI. Now it's
real. The question isn't whether
AI replaces companies, it's whether
you're building. While everyone else
is debating.
Follow for more.