A billionaire CEO just fired
over 4,000 employees and replaced
their managers with AI. And
he says this is just
the beginning. Jack Dorsey, the
CEO of Block and co
founder of Twitter, cut more
than 40% of his workforce
in February. But he says
this wasn't about the company
struggling. It was a deliberate
bet on artificial intelligence. His
argument is wild but simple.
He says managers basically exist
to move information up and
down a chain. And now
AI can do that through
a live world model of
the entire business. Every decision,
every plan, every design already
lives as a digital record.
So why do you need
a human middleman? Now every
employee at Block falls into
one of three builders who
make things, problem owners who
drive outcomes and player coaches
who develop talent. No traditional
managers. AI is the org
chart. If this works, every
company in the world is
going to copy it. The
question is, does your job
survive that shift? Follow for
more.