Everyone said OpenAI was falling
apart. Code Reds Sora shutdown
Anthropic stealing enterprise deals. So
what did they do? They
just closed a $122 billion
fundraise, the largest single raise
in venture capital history at
an $852 billion valuation. Amazon,
Nvidia and SoftBank put up
110 billion of it alone.
But here's the number no
one's talking about. OpenAI is
pulling in 2 billion a
month in revenue, and over
40% of it is enterprise
on track to match consumer
by year end. They didn't
panic. They skated to where
the money was heading. Now
they're merging ChatGPT, Codex and
their agent tools into a
single unified super AP. Sora's
gone, the side quests are
over. This is OpenAI going
all in on becoming the
operating system of a 852
billion says the market believes
them, but Amazon's deal reportedly
has an AGI clause that
resets everything. Follow for more.
This story's
far from over.