OpenAI blindsided Disney, one of
the biggest companies on earth,
with less than one hour's
notice before killing the product
they were actively building together.
According to a Wall Street
Journal investigation, Sora was hemorrhaging
roughly $1 million a day
in compute costs. Disney was
already piloting an enterprise version
for marketing and VFX with
a spring launch on the
calendar. So OpenAI pulled the
plug and funneled all those
freed up chips into a
secret internal model codenamed Spud,
built to go after coding
and enterprise customers and directly
counter anthropic Sora 3 training
was literally about to begin,
that potential billion dollar Disney
partnership now effectively dormant. And
apparently that's how OpenAI handles
its most important relationships. A
text less than an hour
before the world finds out,
would you trust OpenAI as
a business partner after this?
Let me know in the
comments. Follow for more AI
deep
dives.